[{"created":"11/4/2019 14:19:01","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848341000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"Notice and reduce the amount of paper you print"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:20:10","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848410000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Use energy efficient lightbulbs"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:20:41","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848441000,"question":"I‚Äôm a green champion when I‚Äôm out and about!","questionType":1,"answer":"Use reusable metal / glass straws instead of taking plastic straws"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:22:40","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848560000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"Recycle newspapers"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:23:29","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848609000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"Use the recycling bins in the office"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:23:40","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848620000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"Bring your own reusable coffee cup, lunchbox, cutleries for takeaways"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:23:49","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848629000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"Be mindful of the water you use"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:24:02","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848642000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"Switch off computer screens when not in use"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:24:15","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848655000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"Bring a desk plant to office"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:24:25","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848665000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"Using eco-friendly office supplies (recycled paper notebooks etc.)"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:24:45","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848685000,"question":"I‚Äôm a green champion when I‚Äôm out and about!","questionType":1,"answer":"Buy products made of recycled material, eg paper, packaging"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:24:56","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848696000,"question":"I‚Äôm a green champion when I‚Äôm out and about!","questionType":1,"answer":"Opt for e-tickets"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:25:07","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848707000,"question":"I‚Äôm a green champion when I‚Äôm out and about!","questionType":1,"answer":"Taking public transport or consider carpooling"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:25:18","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848718000,"question":"I‚Äôm a green champion when I‚Äôm out and about!","questionType":1,"answer":"Consider renting green cars (eg. BlueSG electric cars)"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:25:36","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848736000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Turn your computer off at night"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:25:46","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848746000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Use a clothesline instead of a dryer"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:25:54","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848754000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Adjust the temperature"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:26:04","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848764000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Switch off lights, air-conditioning, electrical equipment and power points when not in use"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:27:20","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848840000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Separate your waste into recyclable and non-recyclable waste"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:27:29","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848849000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Use a water filter or boil water instead of buying bottled water"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:27:39","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848859000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Read up about recycling ‚Äì know what you can and can‚Äôt recycle"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:27:50","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848870000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Meatless Mondays! / Reduce eating meat"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:28:00","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848880000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Cancel your paper bank statements"},{"created":"11/4/2019 14:28:10","createdDate":4,"createdTime":1572848890000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Buy local food to reduce carbon footprint"},{"created":"11/5/2019 9:36:14","createdDate":5,"createdTime":1572917774000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Do not open the fridge door for too long"},{"created":"11/6/2019 14:42:10","createdDate":6,"createdTime":1573022530000,"question":"I‚Äôm a green champion when I‚Äôm out and about!","questionType":1,"answer":"I cycle to work!"},{"created":"11/6/2019 14:43:33","createdDate":6,"createdTime":1573022613000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"Turning off client's meeting room lights when not using."},{"created":"11/6/2019 14:53:05","createdDate":6,"createdTime":1573023185000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I use my laundry water to flush the toilet"},{"created":"11/6/2019 14:54:16","createdDate":6,"createdTime":1573023256000,"question":"I‚Äôm a green champion when I‚Äôm out and about!","questionType":1,"answer":"I recycle my used magazines"},{"created":"11/6/2019 15:06:29","createdDate":6,"createdTime":1573023989000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Used newspaper as table mats"},{"created":"11/7/2019 10:03:14","createdDate":7,"createdTime":1573092194000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"Do not tabao with plastic containers, instead bring my own tupperware"},{"created":"11/13/2019 13:43:20","createdDate":13,"createdTime":1573623800000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I shower faster"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:09:56","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573697396000,"question":"I‚Äôm a green champion when I‚Äôm out and about!","questionType":1,"answer":"I usually bring my own bag for shopping."},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:11:29","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573697489000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I usually put a timer for my aircon"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:25:14","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573698314000,"question":"I‚Äôm a green champion when I‚Äôm out and about!","questionType":1,"answer":"Use public transport and bicycle"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:28:09","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573698489000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"I print less and use my reusable cup"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:28:54","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573698534000,"question":"I‚Äôm a green champion when I‚Äôm out and about!","questionType":1,"answer":"I‚Äôm using my own bag when shopping and refuse any plastic bags"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:30:54","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573698654000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Eat less / less meat !"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:35:08","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573698908000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"Print less or go paperless"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:35:22","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573698922000,"question":"I‚Äôm a green champion when I‚Äôm out and about!","questionType":1,"answer":"Minimise use of disposables"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:35:59","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573698959000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"Go paperless"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:36:26","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573698986000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"Reduce paper wastage"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:37:28","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699048000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Turn off the lights when u leave the room"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:37:36","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699056000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Bring my own cup, flush, straw, cutleries"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:38:11","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699091000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"We recycle paper and plastic bags"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:38:25","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699105000,"question":"I‚Äôm a green champion when I‚Äôm out and about!","questionType":1,"answer":"Reusable cup etc"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:39:09","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699149000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Recycle, reduce consumption"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:39:22","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699162000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"I try not to print unnecessarily"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:39:46","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699186000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Recycling"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:40:09","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699209000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"Ensuring all recycled items have been properly handled in recycled bins."},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:40:10","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699210000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"Globally set monitors to sleep at night"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:40:11","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699211000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Avoid plastic bag"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:40:17","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699217000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Switching of electricals"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:40:30","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699230000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Recycle waste"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:41:27","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699287000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Limit the use of plastics items"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:41:35","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699295000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Reduce wastages"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:45:48","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699548000,"question":"I‚Äôm a green champion when I‚Äôm out and about!","questionType":1,"answer":"Recycle newspaper"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:47:07","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699627000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Paperless, sort and recycle litter, use less plastic"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:47:28","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699648000},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:48:13","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699693000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"Use printed paper as recycled paper for notes"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:53:10","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699990000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:53:19","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573699999000,"question":"I‚Äôm a green champion when I‚Äôm out and about!"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:57:54","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573700274000,"question":"I‚Äôm a green champion when I‚Äôm out and about!"},{"created":"11/14/2019 10:57:59","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573700279000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!"},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:00:16","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573700416000,"question":"I‚Äôm a green champion when I‚Äôm out and about!"},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:01:01","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573700461000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"Not printing when I can."},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:02:05","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573700525000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!"},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:02:13","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573700533000,"question":"I‚Äôm a green champion when I‚Äôm out and about!"},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:03:22","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573700602000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!"},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:05:04","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573700704000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!"},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:05:04","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573700704000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!"},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:05:30","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573700730000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Recycle bags"},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:07:35","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573700855000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!"},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:10:08","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573701008000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!"},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:10:29","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573701029000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"Use recycle paper"},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:10:34","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573701034000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!"},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:10:57","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573701057000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Recycle plastic bags"},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:11:19","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573701079000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!"},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:12:13","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573701133000},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:13:34","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573701214000},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:13:47","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573701227000,"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Starting a mushroom farm! üçÑ"},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:18:13","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573701493000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!"},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:18:27","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573701507000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"Recycle papers"},{"created":"11/14/2019 11:20:18","createdDate":14,"createdTime":1573701618000,"question":"I help save the planet at my workplace!","questionType":0,"answer":"üå≤üå≥üå¥üåªüåµüå±üåºüå∑üå∫üåπüå∏üåæüåø‚òòÔ∏èüçÄüçÅüçÇ"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"90% of the food we consumed is home cooked, so there is no wastage."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Aircon used at the minimal to avoid electricity wastage and also to curb the carbon foot print."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"As a family we have pledged that each of my kids is going to plant a tree every year from their 10th birthday onwards before demanding a birthday cake or present :)"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Ask my helper to bring boxes and bags when going to market to buy food"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"At home, my family & I sort out the used plastic bottles and paper/cardboard materials/packaging for weekly disposal at my apartment's recycle bins"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"At home, we eat pure vegetarian diet with no Onion and Garlic."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Bottles are thrown to recyclable bins to help out in segregation."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"By training my 3-year old toddler not to use straws, recycling, reusing glass food bottles and jars, reduce use of Gladwrap and zipper bags"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Choose to cycle than to use my car (unless family activity)."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Collect for recycling of plastic bottles"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Conserve water/fix water leakages asap"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Control and minimize usage of electricity Usage of electricity by switching off electrical equipment when not in use."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Elimination of one use plastic"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Ensure lights/electrical appliances are switched off when not in use"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"fan for sleeping when weather is cool, aircon at 26 degrees if weather is hot."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I ask my family members to follows the same. Unless necessary/can use don't buy anything (including food)"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I do not use disposable cutleries at home."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I don't ask for plastic bag when not required"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I have water saving equipment installed on my taps to improve water usage efficiency"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I make sure that I turn off electricity at home when not in use."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I opt for e statements."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I practice what I preach, and I commit to taking massive action in all areas starting at home."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I preach my kids ,not to waste paper ,which will result in tree being cut ."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I recycle plastic bottles as much as I can."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I recycle whenever I can at home."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I recycle where possible, reduce food wastage by buying what I need (as compared to bulk)."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I separate the trash in plastic and paper and bring to the recycle bin. Even when eating takeaway meals, I use my own non-disposable cutlery."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I try not to use toilet papers and tissues papers at home, replace with water and towel for self-hygiene purpose."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I try to practice during energy consumption by keep aircon temperature to  25degree Celsius and above"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I try to recycle stuff or donate instead of discard."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I try to reduce water usage by taking short showers and switching off the water when not using it because EVERY DROP COUNTS!"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I try to save and recycle as much as I can"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I Turn off light and electronics when not in use"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I turn off the tap when brushing etc not using to conserve water."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"I use biodegrable plastic bag and avoid single use plastic bag whenever possible"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"keep bathing time short"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Lights/fans are switched off in the rooms not in use. We have planted good amount of Plants at home which brings us joy and good air quality."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"make house clean and donate what is not used and just stay at home."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Off lights when not required"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Practicing that influencing my husband and friends to practise the same"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Print less"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Purchased only energy efficient home appliances such as washing machine, aircon and fridge."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Re-purposing, recycling, or buy used"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Re-use batteries and light bulbs where possible"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Recycle beer bottles"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Recycle materials, as well as make our own compost for the garden"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"recycle my trash."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"recycle my waste and never use plastic bags at markets"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Recycle water - reuse water from washer for washing balcony."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"recycle what is possible to recycle"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Recycle, Reuse and Reduce!"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Recycle!"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Recycling plastics and bring my own bag for groceries."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"recycling, telling my kids to stop the aircon when unnecessary and save water and electricity"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Reuse the core of toilet roll for art and craft. Do not take utensils when ordering food delivery"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"reuse water from washing machine to wash toilets"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Save electricity to reduce carbon emission."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Save water and electricity - switch on only when needed."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Segregate waste"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Segregating items that can be recycled"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Separate recyclable from trash"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Start by reduce consumption of products, opt for used items where possible and recycle all recyclable items"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Switching of lights when not in use."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Turn on the lights only when necessary."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Turning off lights, limit A/C"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"use biodegradable rubbish bags, avoid onetime use cutlery, Avoid plastic bag usage by carrying own cloth / jute bags for marketing and shopping."},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Use coffee grounds in the office on the plants at home!"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Use less plastic"},{"question":"I practice what I preach ‚Äì starting at home!","questionType":2,"answer":"Use less plastic bags"}]